Interfaith Worker Justice Records Digital 6414 (d)
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Interfaith Worker Justice Records Digital
1994-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Interfaith Worker Justice
6414 (d)
0.58 cubic feet
0.6 linear ft.
Digital, floppy disks, cd- rom.
Miscellaneous floppy disks and CDs, with some of the records and information from Interfaith Worker Justice.
9431542
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, May 04, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, May 26, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6414: Interfaith Worker Justice Records 6414 AV: Interfaith Worker Justice Audio-Visual Materials 6414 G: Interfaith Worker Justice Records Posters 6414 MB: Interfaith Worker Justice Memorabilia
Interfaith Worker Justice (Organization)
9431542
- W + K Steel: 12/11/2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Not in My Backyard (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Organizing Training, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Training - 1996/1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Training - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Bobo Files (Box 4, Folder 23)
- February 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Fauazza 1/11/1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Poultry (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Dorothy + Gaylod Donneley.doc (Box 4, Folder 27)
- National Committee #2 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- NICWJ #6 - 1997 (Oct.) (Box 4, Folder 29)
- December 2/2000 - Minutes (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Employers (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Poultry Overview 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Advisory Committee - Minutes: March 15, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Workshop Disk 2 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Workshop Disk 3 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Catholic Social Teaching (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Candidates for Ex. Director - 1/8/2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Discount App. (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Board Meeting: Jan. 2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 42)
- FMCS Board Report: Sept. 2001 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Transfer to K (Box 4, Folder 44)
- New Hire Form; Interview Notes (Box 4, Folder 45)
- National Committee (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 47)
- 1999 Proposal (Box 4, Folder 48)
- NICWJ-#4 3/1997 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- NICWJ #5 - 7/1997-9/1997 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Ken Bundy's Proposal (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Tom Cochran article (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Poultry Report: April 1999 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Sedaqah.wpd (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 58)
- GA Wkr. Rights Manual - 2/16/1999 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Board of Director (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Kathy Sell - 7/1/1997 // NICWJ Project - 8/12/1997 // Nursing Home Proposal (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Kim - Barb's SEIU piece 6/20 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Sample Labor Day Speakers Program (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Bd rpt 4/1997 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Seminaries (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Floppy Disk - Untitled (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Rev Bundy word does Trade Union Apprenticeship return to the (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Implementation of Building Budgets (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Chicago 1997 + 1998 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- ICWI - #7, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- ICWI - #6, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Inter Committee (3) (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Gainesville (Box 4, Folder 75)